nintendowire.com 2019-11-22

# Privacy policy | Nintendo Wire

## **Privacy Policy for Nintendo Wire**

At Nintendo Wire, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This privacy policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by www.nintendowire.com and how we use it.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our privacy policy, don’t hesitate to contact us through email at contact@nintendowire.com.

### Log files

Nintendo Wire follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this, as well as record analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

### **Cookies and web beacons**

Like any other website, www.nintendowire.com uses cookies. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize users’ experiences by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.

Manage Cookie Settings

### **DoubleClick DART cookie**

Google is one of a third-party vendor on our site. It also uses cookies, known as DART cookies, to serve ads to our site visitors based upon their visit to www.nintendowire.com and other sites on the internet. However, visitors may choose to decline the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at the following URL – [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### **Our advertising partners**

Some of the advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners include:

  * Google
  * Amazon
  * CJ Affiliates (ThinkGeek and Build-A-Bear)

Each of our advertising partners has its own Privacy Policy for their website. For easier access, an updated and hyperlinked resource is maintained here:

Nintendo Wire is also a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon. 

### Privacy Policies

You may consult this list to find the privacy policy for each of the advertising partners of Nintendo Wire

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on www.nintendowire.com, which are sent directly to users’ browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that www.nintendowire.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

### Third party privacy policies

Nintendo Wire’s privacy policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these privacy policies and their links here: [privacy policy links](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browser’s respective website.

We use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may be served from our third party advertiser, you can view their [privacy policy](https://www.network-n.com/network-privacy-policy/) and [cookie policy](https://www.network-n.com/network-cookie-policy/) here. You can manage your cookies here 

We use Google Analytics and Comscore to analyse the use of our website. Google Analytics and Comscore gather information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google’s privacy policy is available at: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). Comscore’s privacy policy is available at [https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy](https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy).

### Online privacy policy only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect at www.nintendowire.com. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

### Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms and conditions.
